[{"id":140,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a text area?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"textbox\">","answer_b":"<textarea>","answer_c":"<input type=\"textarea\">","answer_d":"<textbox>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_b","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":499,"question":"Which of the following attribute triggers event when the length of the media is changed?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"ondrop","answer_b":"onended","answer_c":"onemptied","answer_d":"ondurationchange","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":146,"question":"Which HTML element defines the title of a document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<title>","answer_b":"<head>","answer_c":"<meta>","answer_d":"<start>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":486,"question":"Which of the following is a declaration for an HTML document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>.....<\/html>","answer_b":"<p>.....<\/p>","answer_c":"<!DOCTYPE Html>","answer_d":"<body>.....<\/body>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":539,"question":"How can we define a Video Tag in HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<video src \"URL\"><\/video>","answer_b":"<video src=\"URL\"><\/video>","answer_c":"<video><\/video>","answer_d":"<video src:\"URL\"><\/video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":533,"question":"In HTML document the tags","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Should be written in upper case","answer_b":"can be written in both uppercase or lowercase","answer_c":"should be written in propercase","answer_d":"should be written in lower case","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":513,"question":"Outlook Express is a _________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"E-Mail Client","answer_b":"Browser","answer_c":"SearchEngine","answer_d":"None of the above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":447,"question":"The BODY Tag is usually used after","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"EM Tag","answer_b":"HEAD Tag","answer_c":"HTML Tag","answer_d":"TITLE Tag","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":492,"question":"Which of the following tags represents a section of the document intended for navigation in HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"footer","answer_b":"dialog","answer_c":"section","answer_d":"nav","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":479,"question":"HTML tags are surrounded by which type of brackets.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Curly","answer_b":"Angle","answer_c":"Squart","answer_d":"Round","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":491,"question":"Which of the following is true about HTML 5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"HTML5 is the next major revision of the HTML standard superseding HTML 4.01, XHTML 1.0, and XHTML 1.1.","answer_b":"HTML5 is a cooperation between the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Web Hypertext Application Technology Working Group (WHATWG).","answer_c":"HTML5 is a standard for structuring and presenting content on the World Wide Web","answer_d":"All of These","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":453,"question":"A simple text file which tells the browser what to cache Is known as a\/an ________.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Input Files","answer_b":"HTML File","answer_c":"A Manifest File","answer_d":"Output Files","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":471,"question":"Apart from the <b> tag, what other Tag makes text bold ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<emp>","answer_b":"<strong>","answer_c":"<fat>","answer_d":"<black>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":158,"question":"Which input type defines a slider control?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"slider","answer_b":"search","answer_c":"range","answer_d":"controls","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":494,"question":"Which of the following is true about Cookies?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Cookies are limited to about 4 KB of data . Not enough to store required data.","answer_b":"Cookies are included with every HTTP request, thereby slowing down your web application by transmitting the same data.","answer_c":"Cookies are included with every HTTP request, thereby sending data unencrypted over the internet.","answer_d":"All of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":151,"question":"What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<movie>","answer_b":"<media>","answer_c":"<type=\"video\">","answer_d":"<video>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_d","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":139,"question":"What is the correct HTML for making a drop-down list?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<input type=\"dropdown\">","answer_b":"<input type=\"list\">","answer_c":"<select>","answer_d":"<list>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":512,"question":"Text within <EM> \u2026 <\/EM> tag is displayed as ________","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"bold","answer_b":"indented","answer_c":"list","answer_d":"italic","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":156,"question":"The HTML <canvas> element is used to:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"draw graphics","answer_b":"display database records","answer_c":"create draggable elements","answer_d":"manipulate data in MySQL","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":476,"question":"What should be the first tag in any HTML Document?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<html>","answer_b":"<!doctype html>","answer_c":"<title>","answer_d":"<head>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"}]